Finally done.
Okay, I'm going to take off.
Nakano!
Sorry!
Huh?
The other team's project is all messed up!
You've got to help!
Ugh, I don't want to!
Please!
All right.
Thanks! You're the best!
Holding darkness within brings
one's world to ruin.
Before that happens,
we must save him.
I will go to him.
What? You're going?
He must be freed of his
troubled heart, right?
It'll be easier this way.
Well then, would you like to give it a shot?
Mmm!
No way! Really?!
I'm going to pamper him
to his heart's content!
Kuroto, it's mom. How are you?
We observed the 6th anniversary
of Grandma's passing today.
Everyone is doing well.
Will you make it home for the Obon festival?
Keep in touch, okay?
The last train, again.
And I skipped dinner.
Did I eat the last of that instant ramen?
Eh, whatever.
If things go on like this,
I'll collapse before long.
Something smells good...
Huh? Did I forget to turn off the lights?
Welcome home!
You've had a long day, haven't you?
Huh? Sorry, wrong apartment!
No, this is mine...
Welcome home!
You've had a long day, haven't you?
What the...?
I'm not dreaming.
Then...
Welcome home!
You've had a long day, huh?
I've been waiting for you.
Dinner is all ready to eat!
Why is there a little girl in my apartment?
And one with big ears and a tail, no less!
Maybe she lives in the neighborhood?
But if someone were to see her here...
I always knew he'd end up
doing something like that!
I am so sorry for my son's behavior!
I didn't see anything.
I just need to get to bed...
I can tell you're quite worn out.
What?! You can move through walls?!
A-Are you a ghost?!
Wow, it's built up quite a bit.
Aren't you going to have dinner?
Huh?
I warmed it up for you.
You must be hungry after working so late.
Mmm! I'll dish it up right away!
Hold on a second here!
What the hell are you?
And what are you doing in my apartment?
Oh... I put my heart into
making this meal for you, but...
Oh, well. I guess I'll toss it out.
A-All right! I'll eat it, I'll eat it!
Splendid!
It looks delicious.
Fresh-cooked!
I can't eat that much!
No need to hold back!
Thank you.
Mm-hmm!
This is awkward.
What do you think? Not bad, huh?
It's delicious!
Is it?
How about the stew?
It's sweet and rich....
Hmm, you know--it's like
the food grandma used to cook!
Is that a good thing?
Yeah!
Well then...
I'll have some, too!
Somehow, this takes me back...
I wonder how many years it's been...
Mmm, delicious!
How long since I came home to a hot meal...
...and ate with another person...
Would you like seconds?
Oh, yes. Thank you.
Wait! Who is this kid?
Don't you think it's about time you told me?
Hmm?
Who you are?
Ah, yes.
My name is Senko!
I'm an 800-year-old servant
of the gods--a demigod fox!
A demigod... fox?!
You're a demigod fox... named Senko?
That's right!
And you're 800 years old?
But you look just like a kid...
I told you, that's too much!
No need to hold back.
There's more of the stew, too!
You didn't get these ingredients
from my kitchen, did you?
I brought them myself!
Oh...
They're very good. Where did you buy them?
Oh, they were just offerings
people made at the shrine.
I'm not sure I should be eating that...
Is something wrong?
No... I just...
Why did you come here?
I couldn't stand to see
you looking so haggard,
so I came to help you!
Haggard?
I mean, I appreciate the help,
but why are you going through
all this trouble for me?
Listen carefully.
O-Okay.
The truth is, you are...
Uh-huh...
...just the type of handsome boy I like!
That's it?!
What do you mean, "that's it"?
Oh, no, I mean... I guess gods
can do whatever they want, huh?
I am indebted to your family.
Huh?
You could call it the whims of divinity.
All you need to do is accept the pampering.
Okay...
Thanks for making dinner.
It was my pleasure.
Did everything taste good?
Fantastic, I stuffed myself.
I'm glad to hear it.
And this tea is great, too.
Well then, it'll be tea
after every meal from now on.
I think all that coffee you drink
is disturbing your stomach.
What? How do you know about that?
I've been watching you
quite closely for a while.
Closely? Oh, I'll take those.
You sit down. Just keep quiet
and accept the pampering.
Hang on--
Please, your tea is getting cold.
A lucky tea stalk...
Would you like a snack, Kuroto?
Yeah!
Ooh!
Grandma, look!
I didn't have any hojicha either, did I?
No, I brought some.
Sorry about that.
Why are you apologizing?
Come now, just sit back
and let me pamper you!
I'm not sure I know how to be pampered...
If you need anything, just say so!
There is one thing.
Uh-huh?
Would you mind if I touched your tail?
M-My tail?!
Oh, no, if that's not okay
with you, it's fine...
W-Well, if you must...
I... I wouldn't normally do this, you know.
Goodness!
You're a strange one, aren't you?
You think so?
All right, then, go ahead.
Incredible...
This brilliant golden fur...
It's an overwhelming
explosion of shiny fluff!
Are you sure you don't mind?
Just get on with it.
Oh, yeah...
So fluffy...
Eep!
Mmm, so soft... I could do this forever.
This must be the most
luxurious fur in existence.
It's like being completely
enveloped in a gentle hug.
Could you perhaps tone it down a little?
Eep!
Sorry, does that tickle?
It's fine, pay it no mind.
You may continue as long as you want.
Okay!
Eeeep!
Thank you very much.
Feel better?
Like a new man.
I'm just glad to see you happy.
Sorry, I messed up your fur.
I felt like I was petting our family cat,
and kind of lost myself.
No problem! It's just been fluffed up!
You've done so much for me tonight,
and I can't do anything for you...
How adorable.
Huh?
Seeing a smile on your face
is all I need in return.
Still, I mean...
A guy my age shouldn't be
cared for by a little girl.
Please! Need I remind you
that I'm over 800 years old?
Well, if you go on like this,
I'll end up a lazy bum.
Is that really a problem?
Everyone has their faults.
Even me, and I've had 800 years
to work them out.
I think you're working hard enough as it is.
I did all of this for
you because I wanted to.
You need not worry about it.
And, I might add, there's one thing
you're mistaken about.
Mistaken?
A demigod fox's care is priceless--
No number of good deeds
could possibly add up to that!
All you need to do is enjoy the pampering!
Come now.
You're working so hard.
Just relax and let yourself be pampered.
I'm here to take care of you.
Grandma! Where are you?
Over here.
Huh?
Wait!
Kuroto!
Grandma!
Did I fall asleep?
Hmm, did you?
Could it be?
Your complexion has improved.
And you're much more relaxed now.
Huh? Now that you mention it,
my body feels lighter.
Thank you so much!
Please, no need to thank me.
I've only just begun pampering you!
You've much to look forward to!
Can I touch your tail again?
That you can only do once a day!
"Super Senko-san Time"
Welcome home!
You've had a long day.
Come in, come in!
You just let me handle everything!
Here we are!
Houjicha, one of my favorites.
Do you like the aroma? And the taste?
Oh, good.
Shall I teach you how
to brew houjicha just right?
Mmm! All right, then.
The trick is to pour
the hot water into the teapot
and then wait a little while.
And, think to yourself, "I wish
for deliciousness," as you pour it out.
How's that?
Mmm! A cup of tea before bed
brings joy and soothes the soul--
I highly recommend it.
Thanks for all your hard work today.
A good night's sleep will have you
feeling fresh tomorrow.
Sleep well, then. Good night!